A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2002-2009 (bulk 2005-2009)
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Constituent correspondence, 2006-2009., Extent: 7.5 boxes (2.65 cu. ft.).
  - 2700069-2700996, 2007 October. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 2701010-2701078, 2007 October. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 2701101-2701557, 2007 October. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 2701270-2701911, 2007 October. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 2702001-2702766, 2007 November. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 2702865-2704545, 2007 November. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 2706002-2709948, 2007 November. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 2710064-2714202, 2007 November-December. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 2714511-2718893, 2008 January. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 2719081-2719997, 2008 January. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 2720011-2721761, 2008 January-February. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - 2721861-2728857, 2008 February. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - 2731858-2739593, 2008 March-April. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 2740279-2744363, 2008 April-May. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 2746095-2750258, 2008 May-June. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 2760064-2763545, 2008 July-August. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 2763624-2764903, 2008 August-September. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 2765032-2766293, 2008 September. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - 2766313-2769824, 2008 September. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 2770030-2770996, 2008 September. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - 2771039-2774543, 2008 September-October. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - 2776159-2778632, 2008 October. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - 2779119-2779602, 2008 October. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - 2780010-2789770, 2008 October-November. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - 2790304-2791999, 2008 December-2009 January. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 2792332-2792945, 2008 December-2009 January. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 2794187-2795488, 2009 January. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 2796025-2799488, 2009 January-February. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 2800685-2805934, 2009 February. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 2810194-2812946, 2009 March. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 2813437-2816939, 2009 March. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 2817174-2819650, 2009 March. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 2820645-2829983, 2009 March-April. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 2830016-2833829, 2009 April-May. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - 2834163-2835607, 2009 May-June. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - 2836026-2838534, 2009 June. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 2840289-2843522, 2009 June. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 2844391-2849062, 2009 July. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 2850522-2859947, 2009 August-October. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 2861621-2869043, 2009 October-November. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - 2867470-2872997, 2009 November-December. (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Series III: Deputy Director Subject files, 2004-2008., Extent: 1.5 boxes (.60 cu. ft.).
  Series III: Deputy Director Subject files, 2004-2008, is housed in 1.5 boxes and arranged alphabetically by folder title. Included are meeting agendas, reports, and studies.
  - Agriculture and Forestry Transition Policy Committee report, 2006. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Enterprise Act, 2005. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Biodesal Study, 2005. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Cabinet meetings, 2006. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Cabinet meetings, 2007-2008. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Forestry Summit, 2004-2005. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Jack M. Matthews Foundation, 2005-2006. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Speciality Crop Initiative, 2005. (Box 26, Folder 4)